The man the Mafia could not kill
Our Godfather is a documentary, history film directed by Andrew Meier.
The story of how Sicilian Mafia boss Tommaso Buscetta (1928-2000), the Godfather of Two Worlds, revealed, starting in 1984, the deepest secrets of
the organization, thus helping to convict the hundreds of mafiosi who were tried in the trial held in Palermo between 1986 and 1987.
Tommaso Buscetta (voice), played by Nino D'Agata.
Young Stefano Buscetta, played by Brandon Veliz.
Young Roberto Buscetta, played by Filip Kiritsis.
Self - Buscetta's 3rd Wife, played by Cristina Buscetta.
Self - Buscetta's Son, played by Roberto Buscetta.
Self - PF Officer, played by Roberto Precioso.
The Godfather is a trilogy of American crime films directed by Francis Ford Coppola inspired
by the 1969 novel of the same name by Italian American author Mario Puzo.
The films follow the trials of the fictional Italian American mafia Corleone family whose
patriarch, Vito Corleone, rises to be a major figure in American organized crime.
His youngest son, Michael Corleone, becomes his successor.
The films were distributed by Paramount Pictures and
released in 1972, 1974, and 1990.
The series achieved success at the box office, with the films
earning between $430 and $517 million worldwide.
The Godfather and The Godfather Part II are both seen by
many as two of the greatest films of all time.
The series is heavily awarded, winning 9 out of 28 Academy Award
nominations and 5 out of 20 Golden Globe Awards.
The film explores themes of witness protection, palermo,
sicily, biography, mafia boss, family secrets.
The tone is thought_provoking.